— BRYAN MOSES ←

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

CONTACT



779-875-(6065)



bryancmoses@lewisu.edu

PROFILE

As a computer science student, I have developed many skills essential in most workplaces, including problem solving, critical thinking, leadership, arithmetic literacy, and resourcefulness, among others. I am proficient in Python, Java, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, along a vast understanding of Computer Hardware. Through past employment, I've gained experience in management with a fundamental understanding of the daily operations of a business. I am ambitious and strive to aid the development of the company I'm employed, as well as the team I collaborate with.

SKILLS

- PROBLEM SOLVING
- **DATA ANALYSIS**
- **MANAGEMENT**
- **COMPUTER HARDWARE**
- **PROGRAMMING**

EDUCATION

Lockport Twp Highschool

2016-2020

Attending this high school, I've gained generalized skills essential in the workplace.

Lewis University

2020-2024

Currently enrolled as a student in the computer science department, I am sharpening my skillset in computer programming and problem solving. Skills essential to eventually becoming a software engineer.

EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager

2019-2022

Currently employed as an Assistant Manager at a Sonic Drive-In franchise location, my responsibilities included: optimizing the efficiency of the business, analyzing sales trends, customer support, increasing profitability, recording sales, accounting, inventory, and communicating scheduling with employees. Employment as an assistant manager has helped me develop skills in analytics, leadership, team development, delegation, and accounting. Along with those developments, this position has also provided me with an understanding of the basic operations of running a business.

Banquet Server

2021-2022

Whilst working as a banquet server at Dinolfo's Banquets in Homer Glen, I've enhanced my skills in planning and execution along with customer service. The responsibilities included in this position were, coordinating with the management and utilization of flowcharts to service guests to the highest degree, communicating with the guests to best satisfy their requests, setting tables, cleaning, etc. This position also

Geek Squad Agent

2022-2023

I am currently a Geek Squad Consultation Agent. This position's responsibilities include me being the first point of contact in any technological issue, customer service, and filing multitudes of paperwork.